christyng.com 2014-11-20

# Privacy Policy - ChristyNg Shoes | Shoe Heaven | Wedding Shoes

_Privacy & Cookie Policy_

**Privacy Notice**  
This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for www.ChristyNg.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data
  * The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing  **

ChristyNg.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

ChristyNg.com will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

**Access to and Control Over Information  **

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Orders**    
ChristyNg.com request information from you on our order form. To buy from us, you must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

**Security**  

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.  
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees at ChristyNg.com who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

**Surveys & Contests **

From time-to-time ChristyNg.com requests information via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and you may choose whether or not to participate and therefore disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Contact information will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.  
Christyng.com is committed to protecting the privacy of our site customers and visitors. In efforts to create a safe, secure and pleasant shopping environment, we do not disclose any customer information to any third parties except where it is part of providing a service to you. – e.g. with Fed Ex for the product to be sent to you, carrying out credit and other security checks .

     We will not sell your name, address, e-mails address, credit card information to any third party and we take pride in the safe guarding of our database. 

However, we cannot be responsible or held liable for the actions of any other third party sites from which you may have been linked or directed to the ChristyNg.com website.

**Marketing & Communication**

If you have signed up for our email newsletter or may have made a purchase from our web store or head office, you may receive e-mail communication from us occasionally.  You will also be given the option to opt out of our e-mail newsletter list and opt back in future shall you wish to do so.

**Cookies**

A cookie, also known as a web cookie, HTTP cookie or browser cookie is a small information file that is sent from a website to your computer, mobile or other device while you browse any website. When you browse the same website again in future, the date kept in this cookie can be retrieved by the website to notify the website of the user’s previous activity. Cookies are designed to function as reliable mechanism for websites to recall the state of the website or the activity which the user has made in the past.  You may change the settings on your web browser to prevent cookies from being store in your computer or mobile device without your consent. You may refer to the “help” section of your browser for more information on how to manage cookie settings accordingly.

     **Disclosure of your information**

We may disclose your personal information to any of our group companies. We many also disclose your personal information to third parties based on the following conditions:-

  1. In the event that Christy Ng Sdn. Bhd. Sells or buys any business or assets.
  2. In the event that Christy Ng assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data about our customers may be transferred.
  3. In the event that we are under the duty to disclose and share information in line with complying with tax laws or other forms of legal obligation. This may include exchanging information with other companies or organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**What is a Backorder?**

A backorder is to give another chance for customers to purchase exclusive Christy Ng shoes which are previously soldout. We will open backorders for a limited quantity only, so do place your orders early to confirm your slot.

**How to purchase a Backorder item?**

It's exactly the same as purchasing an in-stock item! The only difference is that you will receive the purchased items by the date as stated on the website.

*Please only purchase when you can wait, as sometimes we are not able to control any external factors on the shipment delayed, and a full credit refund will be made if our shipment is insufficient as per your order.

**Purchasing a Backorder along with an in-stock item**

If you have purchase a backorder item along with an in-stock item(s), we will deliver your in-stock item(s) first. We do not hold any in-stock piece(s) or combine shipping. We provide FREE delivery via Pos Laju throughout Malaysia (any ONE items purchased).
